<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Freeing Ourselves</string>

    <!-- Navigation -->
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Testosterone and You</item>
        <item>Finding Healthcare Allies</item>
        <item>Resources</item>
        <item>Workout</item>
        <item>Nearby Resources</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- Workout -->
    <string name="workout_complete">Workout Completed</string>
    <string name="start_workout_button">Start Workout</string>
    <string name="workout_intro">If your goal is to lose weight and get fit, you must establish a
        weight training and cardio routine. By adding muscle with weight training, you increase your
        metabolism and your ability to burn fat throughout the day. The following three routines were
        designed by Patricia Manuel and serve as a good starting point to developing strength and
        overall fitness. The workout routines are all circuit style with little rest, so they will
        raise your heart level and keep you burning fat. Include 30 minutes of cardio on the days you
        are not weight training to see the best results. These exercises, A-C, are to be performed once
        per week with a day of rest in-between each workout. The goal is to perform each circuit with
        as little rest as possible between each exercise in the circuit. For example, in Workout A,
        Set 1, move from bicep curl to tricep extension to V-Ups. Rest for 30 seconds to a minute and
        then repeat the exercises in Set 1 a total of 1-3 times depending on your fitness level. Rest
        1-3 minutes, depending on your fitness level, before moving on to Set 2 and then Set 3. For
        weighted exercises, pick a weight that allows you to complete the proper number of repetitions
        (reps) with some difficulty. Workout C differs from A and B. There is not a set number of reps,
        but there is a time limit. Each exercise is to be performed for one minute. The goal is to move
        from one exercise to the next with no rest. Rest a minute after completing one circuit in Set
        1 if repeating the set 2-3 times. Rest 3-5 minutes before starting Set 2.</string>

    <string name="title_top">Top Fragment</string>
    <string name="about">Launched in 2010, the Brown Boi Project works to build leadership,
        economic self sufficiency, and health of young masculine of center womyn, trans men,
        and queer/straight men of color - pipelining them into the social justice movement.
        We are a diverse and broad community, driven by a commitment to racial justice,
        gender justice, and transforming our privilege of masculinity into a tool for social change.
        We prioritize support that improves the lives of masculine of center womyn, queer,
        and trans people of people of color; work that transforms the lives of women and girls;
        and introduces new alliances and tools for challenging racism, sexism, homophobia,
        and transphobia across our communities.</string>


</resources>
